当你需要输出应用的调试信息时
When you're logging a message in your app, you need
你需要确认一下你需要输出哪个级别的调试信息
to determine what log level it should be displayed at.
除了在开发环境下之外  Verbose这个级别的日志可是千万不能写进代码的
Verbose logs should never be compiled into your app, except
Debug级别的调试代码会被编译  但是真正运行的时候是不执行的
during development. Debug logs are compiled in, but they're stripped
Error  Warn和Info这3个级别的调试代码则会被执行
out at run time. Error, warn, and info logs are
视频上在显示的代码是是调试 API 的调用时候的样子
all kept. And this is what the logging API looks
第一个参数是调试标签
like. The first parameter is the log tag, which can
一个任意的字符串标识符
be any string that you want to identify the log message.
将这个调试标签在你的类中定义为常量是一个好的习惯
It's good practice to define the log tag as a
通常它可以是你的类名或者应用名
constant in your class. Usually it's the name of your class
第二个参数是真正的调试信息
or the app. The second parameter is the actual log
我们回到Android Debug Monitor这个工具  我们能看到
message. If we go back to monitor, we can see that
这个是调试标签列  这个是
this is the log tag column and this is where
调试的信息  如果你点击这个下拉选框
the log message is. If you click on this drop down
你可以通过日志级别来进行筛选  比如
here you can filter the logs by log level. For example
你可以选择只看所有的错误输出
you can click on Error to see all the error messages.
同样你点击 Warn 之后你就能看到所有警告信息
If you click on warn, you'll see all the warning
以及所有高于警告级别的日志信息
messages as well as anything more severe than that. The
其他的调试级别类似  verbose这个级别意味着
same goes for the other levels. And verbose means that
你能看到所有级别的日志信息
you can see all the logs at all log levels.
特别提醒一下  为了让世界更美好  方便你和其他
As a PROTIP, you should avoid log spam for your sake and
开发者们  你应该尽可能的避免过量的日志信息  日志缓冲区有可能会被填满
the sake of other developers. The log buffer could fill up and important
真正重要的错误信息要么会被缓存清除掉
error messages that you really need to see will either roll of the
要么会淹没在大量的不重要的日志信息中
logs or it will get lost in the sea of unimportant log messages.